CELL PHONE: 772-218-1018
DARIN.M.LEVESQUE@NAVY.MIL
DARINLEVESQUE@GMAIL.COM
WWW.DARINLEVESQUE.COM

DARIN M. LEVESQUE

SUMMARY

A military veteran with ten years of Marine Corps aviation service. Currently coordinating CH-53K Integrated Test Team Operations Department scheduling and planning activities. Providing leadership with weekly standard NAVAIR metrics to support tracking of program schedules. Holds an active secret clearance, and is Defense Acquisition University Level II certified in Program Management.

EXPERIENCE

TEST RESOURCE MANAGER

September 2015 - Present

NAVAIR 5.1.1D, 21593 Three Notch Road Lexington Park, MD 20653

Plan, coordinate, monitor and report test execution data to executive leadership to enable data driven decisions with quantifiable metrics. Integrated government and contractor dissimilar systems to produce metrics package which saves 10 hours of work a week. Complete programmatic forecasting drills on test resources and scheduling for ITT leadership upon request for presentation to the Assistant Program Manager, Test and Evaluation (APMT&E) and the CH-53K Integrated Product Team.

CH-53K DEVELOPMENTAL FLIGHT TEST COORDINATOR

February 2014 – September 2015

Jahn Corporation, 21593 Three Notch Road Lexington Park, MD 20653

Manage Integrated Test Team's aircrew currency and proficiency for proper scheduling. Ensure all documentation required to safely and effectively test is available to the flight test engineers and pilots. Plan, coordinate, monitor and report test execution data weekly to populate NAVAIR standard metrics deck for program schedule tracking of ground and flight test activities. Coordinate with ITT Leadership to develop and refine CH-53K specific metrics with a focus to the flight test portion of the program. Publish weekly/monthly reports to leadership for efficient planning and coordination. Complete programmatic forecasting drills on test resources and scheduling for ITT leadership upon request for presentation to the Assistant Program Manager, Test and Evaluation (APMT&E) and the CH-53K Integrated Product Team.

DEVELOPMENTAL/EXPERIMENTAL TEST CREW CHIEF

February 2012 - February 2014

United States Marine Corps

Provided flight scheduling inputs, served as project officer on various aircrew and ground related tests. Participated in test plan development, execution, as well as deficiency and final report writing.

AIRCREW TRAINING COORDINATOR

November 2009 - April 2011

United States Marine Corps

Managed, scheduled, planned, and tracked training for up to 36 aircrew during the west coast stand up of MV-22 Osprey squadrons. Produced 4 Weapons and Tactics Instructors, 6 Night Systems Instructors, 4 Tail Gun Instructors and 26 fully qualified Crew Chiefs.

CREW CHIEF / FLIGHT ENGINEER

June 2006 - February 2014

United States Marine Corps

V-22 — Flew a total of 1480 flight hours, instructed over 100 students in various flights to prepare them to be fully qualified combat air crewman. Extensive knowledge of troubleshooting aircraft systems in support of flight operations.

CH-46 — Flew a total of 398 flight hours and performed unscheduled and scheduled maintenance actions.

EDUCATION

DEFENSE ACQUISITION UNIVERSITY (DAU) LIFE CYCLE LOGISTICS LEVEL II COMPLETE

October 2013

Completed the following additional DAU courses: CLC-011, ACQ-201A, ACQ-201B.

CREW RESOURSE MANAGEMENT (CRM) INSTRUCTOR COURSE

Spring 2011

A course designed to create instructors to standardize, implement and manage fleet CRM program. Instructors are able to teach and designate CRM facilitators to perform aircrew annual requalification.

WEAPONS AND TACTICS INSTRUCTOR COURSE

Fall 2009

Graduate level Weapons and Tactics course producing squadron training coordinators to ensure fleet standardization

V-22 AIRCREW ORGANIZATIONAL MAINTENANCE COURSE / AIRCREW TRANSITION COURSE

Summer 2006

Transition course at VMM(T)-204 tailored to note the differences between the $\,$ CH-46E and the $\,$ MV-22B

HMM(T)-164 AIRCREW TRAINING COURSE

September 2004 - March 2005

Initial flight training school for aircrew. Concepts taught: Crew Resource Management, Operational Risk Management, OSHA HAZMAT training,

BREWSTER ACADEMY

1999 - 2002

Division II college preparatory school in Wolfeboro NH. Highlights: Yearbook editor, Magna Cum Laude, John Brewster Scholar Society, Proctor.

SKILLS. ABILITIES

√ Secret Clearance

✓ DAU Level II Certified

&

✓ Trained in iTrack & iTest

Excel, Word, PowerPoint

QUALIFICATIONS

✓ HTML, CSS

✓ Linux, VBA,

REFERENCES MAJOR JAMES R. GIBSON

VMMT-204, New River Air Station, NC 910-449-4363

CAMERON R. HAAK

Program Manager, PMA-275, PAX River, MD 301-757-7038

LIEUTENANT COLONEL JON LINDSEY

Executive Officer, MAD PAX River, MD 301-342-1421